RG 062:011, Town of Bloomfield
Connecticut State Library
Town of Bloomfield records
1818-1929
Connecticut State Library
Bloomfield (Conn.)
3 cubic feet
Selectmen, tax, election and school records for the town of Bloomfield.
RG062_011
T000623
Historical Note
The town of Bloomfield was incorporated in May 1835 and was taken from Windsor.
Scope and Content
Selectmen, tax, election and school records for the town of Bloomfield.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Bloomfield -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Bloomfield -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Bloomfield -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Bloomfield -- Registers; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Bloomfield -- Statistics
Places:
Bloomfield (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Cotnainer List
- Records, 1818-1929
  - Lists of electors, 1916-1922 (Box Box 1)
  - Selectmen's correspondence, 1915-1916 (Box Box 1)
  - Tax collectors' records, 1911-1928 (Box Box 1)
  - Rate books, 1877-1920 (Box Boxes 2-3)
  - Tax collection lists, 1919-1922 (Box Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous town records, 1918-1929 (Box Box 3)
  - School enumeration reports, 1818-1823 (Box Box 4)
  - School registers, 1900-1905 (Box Boxes 4-5)
  - Auditors' reports, 1897-1929 (Box Box 6)